# **Bivek Jang Gurung**

# **Results-driven Front-End Developer**

**Location** 32b Hinton Loop, Oran Park, NSW, 2570

**Phone** +61 - 452 424 565

**Email** bivek.tamu@gmail.com

**GitHub** https://github.com/bivektamu/

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/bivek-gurung-b4602a62/

**Portfolio** https://bivekgurung.com/

## **SUMMARY**

Highly skilled Front-End Developer with 7 years of experience building user-friendly and responsive web applications using React, Redux, and modern CSS frameworks. Proven ability to collaborate with designers and back-end developers to deliver successful projects on time and within budget. Increased user engagement by 20% through UI/UX improvements on a recent CMS project.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Front-End Web Developer

Ondicom | May 2017 - April 2024

- Developed over 200+ major web projects over the last 7 years, across various domains such as property industry, healthcare sector, information technology and government.
- Worked closely with management, UX design team and back-end programmers to build the front end of CMS, CRM & associated app development.
- Increased user engagement by 20% through UI/UX improvements on a recent CMS project, Carbon8.
- Developed and implemented the front-end for La Property Co.'s new website,
  resulting in a 15% increase in lead generation through improved user experience and conversion optimization.
- Maintained active conversation with clients to ensure the site met its needs.
- Other duties involved the creation and assembly of responsive email (EDM)
  campaigns, advertising banner, conversion and migration of WordPress websites.

**Technology Used:** React.js, Redux Toolkit, Context Api, RESTful Api, TypeScript, React Testing Library, Vitest, Jest, JavaScript, Node.js, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Tailwind CSS, Material UI, Bootstrap, WordPress, PHP, git, GitHub, Sketch, Figma and Adobe photoshop.

## Web Developer Intern

Thinkun | Jan 2017 - May 2017

- Worked closely with clients to understand project requirements and deliver highquality web solutions.
- Developed custom WordPress themes and plugins to meet client specifications.
- Maintained proper documentation of processes and updates of projects using confluence.
- Developed various custom UI features using JavaScript like shadowboxes, slider carousels, tickers, event calendar filters, language switcher etc. for code reusability.

Technology Used: JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, WordPress, PHP and Bootstrap.

## **EDUCATION**

### Master of IT: Major in Software Development

University of Technology Sydney 2015 – 2017

## **Bachelor of Technology in IT**

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University: Hyderabad, India 2009 - 2013

#### **SKILLS**

Front end: React, TypeScript, JavaScript, jQuery, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, LESS, GSAP

State Management: Redux Toolkit, React Context Api

Css Framework: Tailwind, Material UI, Bootstrap

Back end: Node, Express, RESTful Api, MongoDB, WordPress, PHP,

**Testing:** React Testing Library, Vitest, Jest

CI/CD: Git, Github Actions

Design Tools: Figma, Sketch, Adobe CS Photoshop, Adobe XD, Adobe Illustrator

**Soft Skills:** Time management, Communication, Adaptability, Problem-solving, Teamwork, Leadership and Strong Work ethic.

#### **REFERENCE SITES**

Examples of recent website projects include: -

## **Carbon8 Pty Ltd**

https://www.carbon8.com.au/

## La Property Co.

https://www.lapropertyco.com.au/

## **Dulwich Hill Street Apartments**

https://www.hillstreetapartments.com.au/

## **Drive Property Group**

https://driveproperty.com.au/

## **REFERENCES**

## Arden Majidi

Manager / Senior Front-End Developer at Ondicom

P 0423 472 696

E arden.majidi@ondicomdigital.com

## **Hein Naung**

Back-End Developer at Ondicom

P 0425 226 465

E hein.naung@ondicomdigital.com